vexxhost.com 2019-11-04

# Privacy & Policy - VEXXHOST

Skip to content

Privacy & Policy[Hind Naser](https://vexxhost.com/blog/author/hnaser/ "Posts by Hind Naser")2017-08-17T17:48:32+00:00

Because VEXXHOST, Inc. takes privacy very seriously and wants to protect all of your rights, we have established the following Privacy Policy. Please make sure you understand our policy regarding this matter and feel free to contact us if you have any questions regarding this document.

#### **Personal Information Usage**

VEXXHOST will not search, sell, rent, lend, exchange or give your mail address, your zip code or your phone number at any third party without your explicit permission. The information provided by you is protected and can’t be accessed by anyone else. VEXXHOST, Inc. will only use the customer’s personal information only as reasonably necessary to provide the contracted services.

#### **Disclosure of Personal Information**

The customer authorizes vexxhost to use it’s name, business name, city or country information and comments in marketing documents or as testimonials on our website. At any time, the customer can send a written notice to withdraw this authorization. VEXXHOST, Inc. will only disclose personal information to a third party if requested by law as evidenced by a valid Court Order of competent jurisdiction if needed.

#### **Disclosure of Non-Personal Aggregates**

VEXXHOST, Inc. could share with it’s own partners or third parties a non-personal anonymous aggregate of the information of it’s clients and web site visitors. For example, we could provide statistics data about the number of users of a particular area. The transmitted information will however not reveal in any way your identity.

#### **Orders**

We request information from the user when using our order form. A user must provide their personal information (ex: name, address) & financial information (credit card number, expiration date), this information is all encrypted and will only be used for billing purposes and completing the order itself.

#### **Tracking**

This website uses Google AdWords, Google Analytics, and the Google Display Network together to serve ads to you on other websites after you’ve visited our website. This practice is known as remarketing and is a tool that Google offers to businesses. If you would like to know more about the program, [you can do so here](https://support.google.com/analytics/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=2611268&topic=2611283&ctx=topic). But here are the basics: we, along with third-party vendors, Google and DoubleClick, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

If you would like to opt-out of receiving advertising like this from Google, you can manage these settings by visiting the [Google Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/). Also, Google recommends installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
